Well, just before we wrap up, let me introduce this week's challenge and talk about what we're going
마무리하기 전에 이번 주 과제를 소개하고 뭘 할지 말씀드릴게요
to do.
이것도 아주 재미있을 것 같아요
Hopefully you're finding all of the projects that we're doing together fun.
우리가 함께 하는 모든 프로젝트가 즐거웠으면 좋겠어요
I'm really trying to to come up with with interesting, juicy projects that stretch us in different
여러 방면으로 확장할 흥미로운 프로젝트를 구상 중이에요
So I guess last time we've done, we built things like a system that generates minutes of meetings by
지난번에 했을 때 음성으로 몇 분짜리 회의를 생성하는 시스템을
listening to their audio.
만들었죠
This time something completely different.
이번에는 완전히 다른 걸 할 거예요
It's going to be about writing code.
코드 작성에 관한 거예요
And in particular, the idea is it's going to be about a code conversion, I guess somewhat inspired
특히 아이디어는 코드 변환에 관한 것이 될 겁니다 bloop에서 영감을 받은
by bloop.
것 같네요
And they're fiendishly brilliant idea.
정말 기발한 아이디어예요
So in this case, what we're going to try and do is write a product that is designed to improve performance
이 경우에 우리가 하려는 것은 성능을 향상시키기 위해 디자인된 제품을 만드는 것입니다 파이썬 을 C+로
and performance critical code by converting Python to C plus.
변환함으로써 성능 결정적 코드를 개선하는 것이죠
Plus.
더 있어요
That's the idea.
그게 목적이죠
So we want to to find out how we can convert Python to C plus.
파이썬 을 C+로 변환하는 방법을 알아보려고 해요
Plus.
더 있어요
And we're going to do this using a frontier model.
개척자 모델을 사용할 거예요
And we're also going to do it with an open source model.
오픈 소스 모델로도 할 거예요
And we're going to compare the performance of the results.
그리고 그 결과의 성능을 비교해볼 거예요
But obviously we're going to have to start by selecting llms that are most suitable for the task.
하지만 작업에 가장 적합한 llms부터 선택해야 해요
So that is the challenge at hand.
그게 어려운 점이죠
I think it's going to be fun.
재미있을 것 같아요
We're going to see how we perform at optimizing code with the help of an LLM.
LLM의 도움으로 코드 최적화를 어떻게 수행하는지 보죠
But first, just a quick wrap up for day two of week four.
하지만 먼저, 4주차 둘째 날을 간단히 정리하죠
Let me do that thing one more time.
한 번만 더 할게요
You're probably sick of this, but I do want to remind you of all the things you can do.
이런 얘기 지겹겠지만 당신이 할 수 있는 모든 걸 상기시켜 주고 싶어요
You can code with frontier models, including building AI assistants that use tools.
프론티어 모델과 코드를 만들 수 있습니다 도구를 사용하는 인공지능 조수 제작도 포함해서요
You can now also build open source solutions using hugging face the the Pipeline API across a variety
오픈 소스 솔루션도 구축할 수 있습니다 다양한 추론 작업과 얼굴 포옹 얼굴 포옹, 토큰라이저
of inference tasks and hugging faces, face, Tokenizers and models, which is the lower level APIs
모델 등을 통찰력 있는 낮은 수준의 API를 통해 진행 상황을 파악할
which give you more insight into what's going on and much more flexibility and will become essential
수 있고 유연성도 커지며 나중에 꼭 필요한 기능이 되겠죠
And now?
지금은요?
Now, hopefully you should be in a position where you can confidently choose the right LLM for your
이제 프로젝트에 맞는 LLM을 자신 있게 선택할 수 있는 위치에
project, backed by real results from leaderboards, from arenas, and from other resources.
서길 바랍니다 리더보드, 아레나스 등 여러 리소스에서 얻은 실제 결과에 기반해서요
And when I say choose the right LLM, typically you'd be choosing the right 2 or 3 llms that you will
올바른 LLM을 선택하라고 하면 보통 올바른 2, 3개의 LLM을
then go into prototype with in order to then finally select the one that performs best after next time,
선택하게 됩니다 프로토타입으로 가서 다음 번에 가장 잘 작동하는 것을 선택하기 위해서요 모델의 코딩 능력을
you should have a deeper sense of how to assess the coding ability of models, and you'll have used
평가하는 방법을 더 깊이 아셔야 합니다 코드 생성하기 위해 선구 모델을 사용했고
a frontier model to generate code and built a solution front to back using Llms to generate code.
코드를 생성하기 위해 LM을 이용해 솔루션을 구축했죠
And that's going to be another another skill that you will have acquired on the path to being a highly
숙련된 LLM 엔지니어가 되려면 배워야 할 또 다른 기술이
proficient LLM engineer.
되는 거죠
I will see you there.
거기서 봐요